{"data":[{"question":"She is looking forward to go to Europe after she finishes her studies at the university.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"considering","b":"postponing","c":"the following week","d":"because","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Because-> because of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"They said that the man jumped off of the bridge and plunged into the freezing water.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Having lost","b":"supporting","c":"despite","d":"the objections of","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Supporting-> to support","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. Anderson used to jogging in the crisp morning air during the winter months, but now he has stopped.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"by","b":"are","c":"to enter","d":"within the next","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"I do not know where could he have gone so early in the morning.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Because of","b":"torrential","c":"had devastated","d":"to assist in","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Because of-> because","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The people tried of defending their village, but they were finally forced to retreat.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of sanitation","b":"are","c":"cause of","d":"in some areas of","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The professor was considering postponing the examination until the following week because the students' confusion.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Had the committee members","b":"more carefully","c":"second was","d":"as the first","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- As->than","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Having lost the election, the presidential candidate intends supporting the opposition despite the objections of his staff.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is a major","b":"in those countries","c":"have","d":"by recurrent drought","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Have-> has","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The congressman, accompanied by secret service agents and aides, are preparing to enter the convention hall within the next few minutes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to withdraw","b":"all support","c":"are causing","d":"among","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Because of the torrential rains had devastated the area, the governor sent the National Guard to assist in the clean-up operation.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Underutilized","b":"has been","c":"as","d":"to the famine","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Has-> have","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Lack of sanitation in restaurants are a major cause of disease in some areas of the country.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Because","b":"had worked","c":"diligent","d":"to renovate","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Diligent-> deligently","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}